Contact

mejackson83@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tia-jackson-cordier-msn-agnp-c-20499996 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing BLS

Healthcare

Tia Jackson Cordier, MSN, AGNP-C

Center Director at SynergenX Health Woodlands Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), ABLS, TNCC, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science (MS) focused in Adult-Geriatric Primary Care with an Oncology subspecialty from University of Alabama at Birmingham.

Experience

SynergenX Health 1 year 6 months

Center Director
March 2020 - Present (5 months)

The Woodlands, Texas, United States

Nurse Practitioner February 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months) Houston, Texas Area

Assistant Center Director September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months) The Woodlands, Texas

Memorial Hermann Health System RN November 2013 - May 2017 (3 years 7 months)

Gifted Healthcare Travel Registered Nurse May 2015 - November 2015 (7 months) First Choice Emergency Room
Per Diem RN
October 2014 - November 2015 (1 year 2 months)

Tulane Medical Center ER RN November 2011 - October 2013 (2 years)

Ochsner Health System Er RN June 2008 - November 2011 (3 years 6 months)

Education

University of Alabama at Birmingham

Master of Science (MS), Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2016 - 2018)

University of Holy Cross
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2003 - 2008)